http://www.turnstile.com/privacy

Privacy Statement
Perey Turnstiles has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy issues. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for Turnstiles.com.
At Perey Turnstiles, we are very committed to your privacy, so here is our PRIVACY PROMISE TO YOU: Turnstiles.com will never sell, exchange, or release any of your individual personal information to a third party without your express permission.
Information We May Collect
Perey Turnstiles
will only use the information you supply to contact you regarding
an inquiry you have made.
We do not sell, rent or otherwise make available the information you supply us.
Links To Other Websites
Perey Turnstiles may contain links to other sites. Perey Turnstiles is not
responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Perey
Turnstiles does not share any of the individual personal information you provide
Perey Turnstiles with the sites to which Perey Turnstiles links, although Perey
Turnstiles may share aggregate data with such sites (such as how many people
use our site). This includes other third party sites on the Internet for which
Perey Turnstiles provides search services.
Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.
Contacting Perey Turnstiles, Inc.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
site, or your dealings with Perey Turnstiles, please contact:
Privacy Policy Issues
308 Bishop Ave., Bridgeport, CT
06610,
USA
Toll Free 877-TURNSTILE
Tel. 203-333-9400
Fax 203-333-9410
